{
    "id": "0f05019f71254de1938f362c76332a0c",
    "title": "Active And Passive Voice Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He is ..................................... by his own friends.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "being deceiving",
                "being deceived",
                "deceiving"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f154a1305b124c04a20981cfd5035499"
        },
        {
            "question": "Prince Hamlet ........................................ by the people.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "welcomed",
                "was welcomed",
                "has welcomed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cd22b034d2a84df09326438bb88aa4ae"
        },
        {
            "question": "The proposal ......................................... by the committee.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "has rejected",
                "has been rejected",
                "had rejected"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "00c9f302dceb4227a8970372e4e92015"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ........................................ much cause for anxiety.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have given",
                "have been given"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c68b42a12cad4d7da609d3a6666f34e9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Have my orders .............................................. out by you?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "carried",
                "been carried",
                "been carrying"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8e8fca30ef1641c69270ac015dfce8db"
        },
        {
            "question": "The story was eagerly ............................................... to.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "listening",
                "listened"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6c6e20157c4a485ca0cadca8fd8d68d3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Our lives are ........................................... in anticipation.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wasting",
                "wasted"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "026c7b9b42fb43b4907ceb7360e7385f"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tree ......................................... by the storm.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "was uprooted",
                "was uprooting",
                "uprooted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "df9fe80598f8420a91d547ac641fc355"
        },
        {
            "question": "The wounded persons ................................................ to hospital by the police.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "taken",
                "were taken",
                "had taken"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56f563226c3a4bde9fd9640e16be60f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "By whom was this piece of composition ........................................?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "writing",
                "written"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b348bf6588f745dd8506ae040054f712"
        }
    ]
}